Before we get things started,
there's something I want to check.
How about you go ahead
and shuffle those cards?
And, shuffled they are.
What pray tell do you have in mind next?
Now draw a card from the deck.
Which one it is doesn't really
make a whole lot of difference.
But don't show anyone.
Very well.
And now I'll call it.
It's the Six of Hearts.
Next, I think I'll name the
cards from the top down.
Five of Spades, Queen of Diamonds,
Jack of Spades, Ace of Hearts,
Seven of Diamonds, plus the Six of Clubs,
King of Clubs, and Two of Diamonds.
He guessed them all!
And that's after Darby shuffled the deck!
How did you do that?
I could rattle off the
entire deck if I wanted to.
Remember my request from earlier?
While you were shuffling the cards,
Star Platinum was busy memorizing
their order in the deck.
Quite the interesting strategy.
That said,
defeating your plan is a
simple matter of shuffling the
cards in a manner that
obstructs your vision of them.
Are you that dense?
Cheating is going to be damn near impossible
as long as you have me as an opponent.
Just something I thought
you should be aware of.
Okay.
The security seal.
An unbroken seal is an
irrefutable confirmation
that the deck has not been
tampered with in any way.
Well, there's only one Joker here.
Don't see anything unusual.
It's a normal deck.
The page number is 538. 540?
No, page 556.
I still got it.
My ability to discern page numbers
by touch is as sharp as ever.
It's true that Jotaro's Star Platinum
has incredible visual prowess,
but I can remember the placement of
anything simply through the use of touch.
Shuffle them all you want.
I still know the exact
location of every card.
Okay, open the game.
Looks like it's the Ten of Hearts.
I drew the Seven of Clubs.
Then it seems like I'll be dealing.
Alright, I need to shuffle
so Star Platinum can't see.
If you would cut the deck.
Thank you, and now I'll deal.
One for Jotaro, one for me.
I don't understand. What happened?
Jotaro! His finger!
Why the devil would you use Star
Platinum to break Darby's finger?
Like I said, you're not going to cheat
when you're playing against me. Huh?
He tried to cheat?
But he was only dealing
the cards, wasn't he?
I didn't notice him do
anything suspicious.
That's what he wanted us to think.
but take a good look at
the cards in his left hand.
I see now!
The second card is sticking out!
That's the card he tried to deal me.
The entire time he was
pretending to deal the top card,
but the truth is he was dealing
me the second card from the top.
That being the case, it means the
top card would have gone to him.
If he'd gotten his hands on it,
the cheating bastard would
have had a total of three tens.
This maneuver is known as the second deal.
A devious sleight-of-hand technique
involving the dealer throwing out the
second card in the deck instead of
dealing the top card as one would expect.
When the technique is
executed by a professional,
the cheat is almost
undetectable to the naked eye.
And if that wasn't enough,
Darby can discern the location of
every card in the deck by touch.
You brutish imbecile!
How dare you break my finger!
I was playing nice with that attack.
You should count yourself
lucky I didn't rip it off.
Good grief.
I guess I can't let you
cut the deck anymore.
Someone else is going
to do it from now on.
That boy on the hill looks up to the job.
Have it your way.
Hey, Avdol, ask him over right away.
Most impressive.
Successful cheating requires
the element of surprise,
and it takes more than
sharp eyes to prevent that.
It appears I underestimated you
as you saw through my second deal.
I'll accept my fractured
finger as proper punishment,
but from here on I'll devote my full
concentration to winning the game.
Jotaro.
I've not done so since my
colossal gamble on May 17th, 1986.
I was playing against a Japanese
man known as Chase Mayama as the
victor my spoils included his eight
Tokyo properties and his soul.
I will say this for Mayama wealth
didn't dull his gambler's instincts.
It's only fair that I warn you I'm
not here on behalf of Lord Dio.
I am here due to the simple
fact that I am a born gambler.
What do you think you're
doing those souls are mr.
Joe stars and Bulgarefs
I've done nothing more than split
their souls into six chips each.
I'm sure you know this, but in poker,
if you're on the verge of losing,
it's perfectly acceptable to fold.
However,
if you use up all the chips for the ante,
there's no way to bet and
the game doesn't work.
To put it plainly,
winning back six chips is the equivalent
of winning the soul of one of your friends.
Makes sense?
All right then, Jotaro.
If you still want to play, you'll have
the opportunity to win back the chips.
But before that, I need
to hear you say the words.
With pleasure.
I'll bet my soul on the game's outcome.
Okay.
Jotaro!
The pure white chips in front of you are
a physical representation of your soul.
Once I procured all six of those chips,
your soul will be added to my collection.
For my opening action, I shall
bet one chip of Polnareff's soul.
Let's begin.
When beginning a new game of poker, each
player is dealt a total of five cards.
Players can improve their
hand by swapping out cards.
Though it seems
straightforward on the surface,
it's the betting aspect that makes poker
a game of determination and psychology.
Now then, what to do?
Ah, I think I'll raise.
Jotaro, you should bear in mind that
those six chips beside you are your soul.
Make sure you think carefully
before making a move.
Listen, it's okay if you don't
understand what's going on.
Don't worry yourself.
You just focus your attention on
cutting and dealing the cards, alright?
Give me three cards.
Would you look at that?
Such a serious glare.
Behind it must be an outstanding hand.
I suppose I'll play it safe for
now and bet one more Polnareff.
Call one.
If you don't fold, you'll need three
chips per game at the very least.
All right, bring it on, Jotaro.
Two pair with eights and nines.
Hmm, that's too bad.
Two pair, jacks and queens.
Oh, no!
My, that was a close one.
I was on the verge of a crushing defeat.
But as it stands...
He only has three left.
Jotaro, what are you...
Okay, next game. Deal the cards.
You should be careful what you wish for.
The next game may well be your last.
I'll change one card.
What's the problem, Jotaro?
Hurry up and check your
hands so you can make
a decision as to whether
you'll change or fold.
Hey, Jotaro?
No, it's fine.
These cards will do.
So sorry. Come again?
There must be some confusion.
Perhaps I misheard you.
I could have sworn I heard
you say these cards will do.
No, you heard right.
I'm fine with these cards.
I'll play the round with this hand.
Obviously!
What I'm trying to ask is,
do you intend to play those cards
without so much as glancing at them?
These cards will do.
Enough subterfuge! Answer me!
How can you play a round
with any sort of confidence
if you don't even look at
the cards in your hand?
Need a favor.
You in?
Favor?
Of course, but answer something first.
Why are you hell-bent on
not looking at your cards?
Damn it, Jotaro!
I demand that you answer me!
Let's see now.
Raise you another two.
While I'm at it, I'll
throw in Avdol's soul.
What?
I admit, you're an
impressive opponent, Darby.
Sure, you're no match for
our stands physically.
But under pressure, you can
be amazingly calm and clever.
Suffice it to say, I'm not much
in terms of being a gambler.
It'd be easy for you
to read me like a book.
So I could never defeat someone like you.
But I have the utmost
confidence in Jotaro.
I don't know why he won't look at his
cards, but that's none of my concern.
If he asks for my soul, I won't
hesitate to put my life on the line.
My soul is in Jotaro's
more than capable hands.
So that's how we're playing this.
It's become apparent
that the two of you have
succumbed to the pressure
of our little game.
You there, I believe
you owe me another card.
Hurry and deal me. Yes, sir.
I dealt just as you asked, Master Darby.
His hand is worthless,
there's no doubt about it.
My skills as a dealer never fail.
You've won.
I know you have.
Jotaro's under the assumption the
boy has nothing to do with this.
But little does he know
everyone in this cafe
and within sight of
this place works for me.
Even the bartender and those men.
No matter what, I can't fail, as my directive
is to make sure Jotaro's hand is weak.
Still, not looking at the
cards was a bold move.
He cut me by surprise, albeit briefly.
It's clearly a bluff.
How dare he bluff against me?
Does the fool really think
I'll lie down and fold?
Huh, very well.
If that's your game, I'll
match you with six Polnare.
And I raise you Joseph's soul.
What do you think?
Fifteen chips total.
What?
Hold on a minute.
That's not fair.
How can you raise your auntie when
Jotaro doesn't have any more chips?
He's out of chips, you say?
There's an easy way to fix that.
What do you mean?
Rectifying your chip conundrum is simple,
as long as my stand
has a written contract.
Once the deal is done, it'll
have Card blanche to take a soul.
And exactly whose soul
are you talking about?
Kakuane's in the hospital.
Why don't you simply bed his soul?
What?!
Panic, fool.
Show me your doubt and fear.
Let me see you lose that cool composure.
How dare he try to bluff me.
After I'm finished with him,
that poker face will be a contorted
ball of anguish and misery.
Sounds like a plan.
I'll see your bed with Kakyoin's soul.
Wait, Jotaro, you can't!
Bedding a man's soul without
his knowledge is so uncouth!
Well, it is kind of selfish.
Hey, Jotaro, what did you just do?
What did I just do?
What do you mean by that?
You lit a cigarette!
What's wrong with you?
Not feeling well or something?
Impertinent!
Why is he so confident?
Could he have...
Could he have used Star Platinum to
swap the cards without my knowing?
Stupid brat, what are you thinking?
Don't look at me with
that worried grimace.
If Jotaro finds out you work
for me, I'll murder you.
Compose yourself, I have four kings.
The only hands that could
beat me are four aces,
a straight flush, or a
joker-led five-of-a-kind.
In order to get his mitts
on any of those hands,
Jotaro would have to
switch all five cards.
A challenge indeed.
With Star Platinum's speed, there's a
chance he could have switched a card.
But five?
Could he really do that right
under my nose? Impossible!
There's no way I could have
missed him replacing all five.
I'm the great Darby, the king of
games, master at the art of gambling.
I've had enough of this, Jotaro.
Your time has come.
He lit that cigarette to psych me
out, so now I know he's bluffing.
You're kidding me!
You got a drink too?
When did you have a
chance to, you bastard?
How dare you make fun of me?
Let's finish this.
My hand is unbeatable. Hold it.
Why are you jumping the gun when
I haven't raised the pot yet?
Raise the pot?
No, you don't have
anything to raise it with.
That's where you're wrong.
I'll raise you with my
mother's soul. What?
Are you out of your mind?
Jojuro, why would you
bet your mother's soul?
The entire reason I came to Egypt in
the first place was to save my mother.
So if I end up losing
here, she'll die anyway.
She won't mind if I bet her soul.
So then, Darby,
for your sake, I hope you have something
to bet that matches my mother's soul.
I know.
For your auntie, I want you to
tell me the secret of Dio Stand.
Judging from his reaction,
He indeed knows Dio's secret.
Unfortunately for him, Dio
doesn't take treason sitting down.
If he tells us the information we
want to know, he's as good as dead.
Jotaro,
if you're confident enough
to bet your mother's soul,
you're sure your hand
will win, aren't you?
You wouldn't let us down, would you?
You've got the winning hand, right?
Jotaro?
Come on, are you going
to call my bluff or fold?
Decision time, spit it out already. Jar B!
I'll say it.
I'll say it, Darmot!
I'll say it!
I'm the world's greatest gambler!
I can do this!
I'll call!
I'm going to call!
Call!
I can't do it.
I'm petrified.
I'm too terrified to say the words!
I can't...
I can't breathe!
That's unbelievable!
His eyes rolled into the back of his head!
How is it possible for someone to
faint while they're on their feet?
He's completely lost it.
The pressure was too much
Mr.
Joestar and Polnareff's souls
are returning to their bodies.
Thank heavens
Mentally he's already forfeited the game
Deep down he knew he had lost.
That's why the souls were released
Four kings!
Are you telling me he
had four kings all along?
Jotaro, I have to know what cards you had
in your hand to inspire such confidence.
Like I thought.
Your hand was shit, absolute shit!
Even with Star Platinum's
incredible speed,
he wouldn't have been able to swap cards?
in front of an expert gambler like Darby.
It's a good thing my
bluff and intimidation
worked so well with such a worthless hand.
Good grief, had I known it was
this crappy, I would have freaked.
What?
What do you mean you'd have freaked?
Jotaro, don't tell me that you bet
our souls on that worthless hand.
It would appear as though his
collection of souls has been released.
Come on, everyone!
Let's play a game of Mahjong!
Backgammon is a lot of fun, too!
Or we can play a game of dice,
even though I don't have any!
Darby of the Osiris Stand! Retired!
I doubt that we'll be able to pry
Dio's secret out of him in this state.
That's true.
He was a formidable opponent.
It's humbling to admit this, but he
almost took us all out single-handedly.
The guy was a force to be reckoned with.
Indeed, he was a fierce adversary.
Ugh, I feel like death warmed over.
Well, I guess we can't be
the heroes in every episode.
Thank you.